this focus we can actually remove it I think because we just can write about the news
and then we can pin it up the news to the favorite ones and probably we can add our favorite
ones though so if you go to any extension an actual dashboard
we'll just remove it to have an hour because now it is annoying okay this one you have to fix
because now we have to type manually but the buttons will not work and we can implement
also the toggle should maybe green so the toggle should be green color when it's selected
and presets like 15 30 minutes should be bigger so this way we can actually use it
okay now we have press buttons I will go back again refresh it and now when I go to the
dynamics it's now clickable but not applying the changes so I want to fix that thing
it's clickable now but it's not applying the changes or it updates the effects indicating
reminder interval it should work now I'll go back again refresh
and now when I go to dynamics reminders 13
everyone housed we can like specify the time but
and keep the design that we can actually add some frameworks
because now we are basic on JavaScript HTML CSS but if you want to change something
we can open new agent and make it more modern design
and now I'll just add as well functionality to have visualization on visualization
based on web browser history use for it
charge JavaScript so this one will add like nice visualization by using this library
and use stone test for all the processing
so we'll add a new frameworks and how we can we know about these frameworks you can know
any Chrome extension and ask about the source code what frameworks were used to build this
and then you can copy to your own source code and use it and I will switch between agent to the list
so you just prepare on my mistake but probably to understand that it's react not tracked
okay for we have a clarification answer the first one migrate everything
and the second option will be
browser history all of the above
and the tone js
refresh replace because it's just web audio API but simple press replace web audio
API with tone js and build up we have a react via cd and simpler no builds that
modern build and now we use actually webpack so we will install the additional libraries
our guide if how we can use it but everything will be written in read me file in the market
down so divide with npm dependencies
and I will post a video first it will just update the total list
it will be updated it will update after the list is a new actually hierarchy this is the build
configuration it will install npm run def build and after that we have eight to the list and I
press build and our extension will change drastically it took a while we have all the functionalities
it's now completely in the order it's our dependencies that have been added and in here we have
it to the list we can add continuum sometimes it's actually post because it has like more than
5000 lines this is the important fixing remaining issues
so go through all the code can close it the installation now
so we have to use the command but still it's fixing a few remaining issues
so as we install npm install we can capital okay now we have it that was a long line
and now we have a dependency so we open first the terminal press npm install
it's loading so it will install all of it
okay at the 75 packages and now I will use npm run build so it will be the extension
this is required if you are using frameworks so it's installed and now the distribution file
have reappeared here we can review it in file explorer so this is how a Chrome extension
it added more than 5000 and then I had to fix it and repeat it again by pressing npm rebuild
I can finally use the extension so this is how design looks like we have a focus you have a news
available browser story with navy nice analytics if syringes in order of it in use I can press here
some models could not work for example and we have to refresh and add our access fit but we can
apply another prompts semi estimated time to do all visits unique domain
so reminders that we can add information so we can add some of the information in reminders
I basically would have to add from the start and personal specify as well
so this way we can create and change all the functionality dynamically
into a Chrome extension but you see other frameworks and have more sleek new design